<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="intro_slide1_title">Let\'s get started</string>
    <string name="intro_slide1_desc">Welcome to <b>andOTP</b>! This wizard will guide you through
        the initial setup process. Please pay attention and read carefully in order to avoid losing data.
        \n\nDon\'t worry, you can still change any of these options later on in the <b>Settings</b>.</string>

    <string name="intro_slide2_desc">To ensure the security of your accounts, <b>andOTP</b> uses
        encryption to store account data. Here you can choose which method of encryption will be
        used.</string>
    <string name="intro_slide2_desc_keystore">The KeyStore is a system component of Android used to
        securely store cryptographic keys. The advantage of using the KeyStore is that the keys are
        stored separately from <b>andOTP</b>\'s data, and can be backed by hardware-based encryption
        (if your device supports it). However, as the keys are not stored with <b>andOTP</b>\'s data,
        <b>this method prevents external backup solutions (like Titanium) from working</b>. If you
        choose this method, you will have to rely on the internal backup functions provided by
        <b>andOTP</b>.\n\n<b>Warning</b>: The KeyStore is known to cause many problems, so
        please only use it if you absolutely have to. If you don\'t mind entering a password / PIN
        every time you start <b>andOTP</b>, it is <b>highly recommended to use the password-based
        encryption instead</b>.</string>
    <string name="intro_slide2_desc_password">This method will encrypt your data with a key
        generated from a password or PIN. The main advantage of using this method is that external
        backup solutions (like Titanium) will work as expected, and it is much less failure-prone
        than the KeyStore. However, you will have to enter your credentials every time you start
        <b>andOTP</b>.</string>

    <string name="intro_slide3_desc_keystore">Here you can setup an authentication method to lock
        <b>andOTP</b>. Since you have chosen <b>Android KeyStore</b> as your encryption method, this
        step is optional.</string>
    <string name="intro_slide3_desc_password">Here you can setup an authentication method to lock
        <b>andOTP</b>. Since you have chosen <b>Password / PIN</b> as your encryption method, a
        password or a PIN must be set to proceed.</string>
    <string name="intro_slide3_warn_no_password">Please set a password to continue!</string>
    <string name="intro_slide3_warn_no_pin">Please set a PIN to continue!</string>
    <string name="intro_slide3_warn_confirm_password">Please confirm your password to continue!</string>
    <string name="intro_slide3_warn_password_mismatch">Passwords must match!</string>
    <string name="intro_slide3_warn_confirm_pin">Please confirm your PIN to continue!</string>
    <string name="intro_slide3_warn_pin_mismatch">Pins must match!</string>

    <string name="intro_slide4_title">Finished</string>
    <string name="intro_slide4_title_failed">Setup failed</string>
    <string name="intro_slide4_desc_failed">Failed to set a password, this intro will be shown again
        the next time!</string>
    <string name="intro_slide4_desc">Your settings have been saved, you are now all set to use
        <b>andOTP</b>!</string>

    <string name="intro_slide_android_backup_desc">Android sync is a feature built in to android used to back up app data to a 3rd party service (usually Google). Backups are always encrypted and unaccessible to 3rd parties without your master password. Requires use of Password encryption method.</string>
</resources>