<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="intro_slide1_title">Welcome to andOTP</string>
    <string name="intro_slide1_desc">This wizard will guide you through the initial setup.</string>

    <string name="intro_slide2_desc">To ensure the security of your accounts andOTP only stores them
        in encrypted data files. Here you can choose which method of encryption will be used.</string>
    <string name="intro_slide2_desc_keystore">The KeyStore is a system component of Android for
        securely storing cryptographic keys. The advantage of this method is that the keys are
        stored separated from the data files and can be backed by hardware cryptography (if your
        device supports it). However, as the keys are not stored with the apps data <b>this method
        prevents external backup solutions (like Titanium) from working</b>. If you choose this
        method you will have to rely on the internal backup functions provided by andOTP.
        \n\n<b>Warning</b>: The KeyStore is known to cause problems on some custom ROMs (and a few
        stock ones as well). If you don\'t mind entering a password / PIN every time you start
        andOTP it is highly recommended to use the password-based encryption.</string>
    <string name="intro_slide2_desc_password">This method will encrypt your data with a key
        generated from a password or PIN. The main advantage here is that this will work with
        external backup solutions (like Titanium). However, you will have to enter your credentials
        every time you start andOTP.</string>

    <string name="intro_slide3_desc_keystore">Here you can setup an authentication to lock andOTP.
        Since you have chosen <b>Android KeyStore</b> as encryption method this is optional.</string>
    <string name="intro_slide3_desc_password">Here you can setup an authentication to lock andOTP.
        Since you have chosen <b>Password / PIN</b> as encryption method you need to set either a
        password or a PIN to proceed.</string>
    <string name="intro_slide3_warn_no_password">Please set a password to continue!</string>
    <string name="intro_slide3_warn_no_pin">Please set a PIN to continue!</string>
    <string name="intro_slide3_warn_confirm_password">Please confirm your password to continue!</string>
    <string name="intro_slide3_warn_confirm_pin">Please confirm your PIN to continue!</string>
</resources>